<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Breathe Life</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Breathe Life</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/profile/quaywest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/profile/quaywest/</guid><description>What is a Film&amp;rsquo;s Post-Production Process? Nunc ac justo, lobortis massa tellus feugiat. Magna pulvinar tortor aliquam turpis vel faucibus ut. Nunc ornare libero nullam quis sem lorem a pharetra non. Ornare ut non in faucibus. Enim, ut id ut enim elementum in. Erat quis senectus felis pharetra quis arcu convallis in. Vestibulum dui senectus adipiscing dignissim duis integer vitae. Faucibus dis nullam vitae malesuada risus pellentesque. Urna amet, elementum facilisis in potenti consequat.</description></item><item><title/><link>/profile/sandiland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/profile/sandiland/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>/blogs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blogs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact us</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Get Involved Today</title><link>/goal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/goal/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GIVE</title><link>/donation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/donation/</guid><description/></item><item><title>GIVE</title><link>/give/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/give/</guid><description/></item><item><title>privacy</title><link>/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy This policy sets out how BreatheLife will handle personal information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 2010 and Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard in light of who we are and who we aspire to be as an organisation.
Our Commitment BreatheLife is committed to protecting the privacy of our donors, supporters, employees and other stakeholders. We value the trust of those we deal with, and of the public, and recognise that maintaining this trust requires that we be transparent and accountable in how we treat the personal information that you choose to share with us.</description></item><item><title>security</title><link>/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/security/</guid><description>Security BreatheLife uses a variety of channels (in-person and digital) to advocate for our cause and raise funds to support our programmes around the world. Unfortunately, fraudsters and cyber crooks are also constantly looking for ways to trick our donors and supporters.
Here are a few common types of fraud:
Phishing via fake websites or emails
Phishing occurs when fake websites or emails are created to look like the official one.</description></item><item><title>testimonials</title><link>/testimonials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/testimonials/</guid><description/></item><item><title>tnv</title><link>/tnc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tnc/</guid><description>Terms of Use Our Commitment BreatheLife is committed to protecting the privacy of the children and adults living in communities where we work. As part of this commitment, BreatheLife prohibits the usage of child photos from our website (breathelife.org.my) on other personal or commercial websites.
Tracking Your Use We collect statistics on visitor traffic to our website through “cookies”. These are anonymous and do not identify you. We may also anonymously track your visit to our website by using information collected by others.</description></item></channel></rss>